BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 52-8-59 (Box 114)
  - Grand Lodge - Group Life Insurance, Officers and Employees: American General Life Insurance Company BRAC Policy 5555, 1971-1972 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    April 20, 1971-December 1972
  - Grand Lodge - Officers and Employees Group Life Insurance Policy 15555 (Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States), 1968-1970 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    April 1968-April 30, 1970
  - Group Life Insurance - Grand Employees: Travelers Accidental Death and Dismemberment, 1964-1969 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Grand Lodge - Officers and Employees Group Life Insurance, 1966-1970 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    January 1, 1966-October 31, 1970
  - Grand Lodge - Group Life Insurance Officers and Employees, 1961-1968 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    1961-May 31, 1968
  - Grand Lodge - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance Plan, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- 59-60 (Box 115)
  - Grand Lodge - Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance, 1961-1967 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Grand Lodge - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance: Canadian Boards of Adjustment, 1960-1970 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Grand Lodge - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance: Canadian Boards of Adjustment, Airline, 1955-1970 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance - General, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Grand Lodge - Grand Presidents Speeches, 1960 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - CEO Speeches and Grand Presidents Speeches, General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Grand Lodge Diorama, 1960 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Lobby Report Information, 1968-1970 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Work Material for Lobby Reports (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Travelers Insurance Company Agreement with Railway Labor Organizations, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Blueprints/Charts (Box 115, Folder 11)
- 300 - 0-323-2 (Box 116)
  - Grand Lodge - Group Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Insurance, 1970-1973 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    September 1, 1970-May 1973
  - Canadian Department Of Labour, 1959-1970 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    December 1959-November 1970. Includes Bound Volume.
  - Canadian Department of Labour - Supreme Court Decisions, 1963 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Canadian Department of Labour - Annual Reports, 1962-1969 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence (Robert King High), 1966-1967 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Carnegie Hero Fund Commission (Transportation Communications Union), 1969 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - General (John Birch Society, Incorporated), 1961-1966 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Court Decisions, 1966-1969 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Court Decisions, 1960-1965 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Court Decisions, 1958-1959 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Acceptances and Declinations - Ground-Breaking Ceremonies, Rosemont, Illinois (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Labor Advisory Committee on Foreign Assistance (Mr. George M. Harrison), 1965 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    May 18, 1965
- 337 - 0-469-0 (Box 117)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1964-1973 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    January 1964-May 1973
  - United States Department of Labor - Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act (Reports), 1960-1969 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    April 1, 1960- 1969
  - Regional Association of General Chairmen - Eastern Region, 1963-1973 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - National Mediation Board - General, 1963-1970 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - National Mediation Board - Annual Reports, 1963-1971 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - National Mediation Board - Unsettled Submissions, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - National Mediation Board - Unsettled Submissions, 1963-1964 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement - General Agreement Interpretation, 1966-1973 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    January 1966-June 1973
- 1-342-82 (Box 118)
  - United States Department of Labor - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1964-1970 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    March 19, 1964-1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - United States Department of Labor - Labor Advisory Committee to the Agency for International Development Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - United States Department of Labor - Conferences, Foreign Visitors, 1960-1969 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - United States Department of Labor - Children's Bureau, 1960-1968 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - President's Committee on Labor-Management Policy, 1962-1964 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    Bound Materials.
  - President's Committee for Equal Employment Opportunity, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - United States Department - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Strikes - General (Telegrams List), 1970 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Strikes - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad (CBQ): Possible Wildcat Strike at Denver, Colorado, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Strikes - Missouri Pacific, Gulf District, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    Section 6 Notice dated July 18, 1966 (Not in Folder)
  - Strikes - Texas and Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    Section 6 notice dated July 15, 1966 (not included)
  - Strikes - Pan Am: Lawsuit Instituted by Pan Am against Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks et al., 1968-1969 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Strikes - Pan American World Airways, Incorporated, 1965-1969 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    Section 1: Contributions for Florida East Coast Strike Members
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    January 1-August 31, 1964. Section 2: Financial Aid for Strike Members
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    September-December 1964. Section 3: Financial Aid for Strike Members (Hardship)
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    January-April 1965. Section 4: Financial Aid for Strike Members
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    May-September 1965. Section 5: Financial Aid for Strike Members (Hardship Fund)
- 342 - 82-115 (Box 119)
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1965-1966 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    October 1965-July 1966. Section 6: Financial Aid for Strike Members (Hardship Fund)
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1966-1967 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    August 1966-July 1967. Section 7: Financial Aid for Strike Members (Hardship Fund)
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1967-1968 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    August 1967-December 1968. Section 8: Financial Aid for Strike Members (Hardship Fund)
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1964 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    April 29-July 15, 1964. Section 9.
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast., 1964 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    July 16-November 8, 1964. Section 10.
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1964 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    November 9-30, 1964. Section 11.
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1965 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    April 1-July 31, 1965. Section 13.
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1966-1968 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    June 1966-December 1968. Section 15.
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1970-1971 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    January 1970-December 31, 1971. Section 16.
  - Strikes - Florida East Coast (Supplementary Materials: Tabulation Tables), 1963-1964 (Box 119, Folder 10)
- 349 - 0-5; 376-2 - 396-4 (See Box 88) (Box 120)
  - Meeting Minutes - Joint Regional Associations (Eastern, Southeastern, Western, Express), 1932 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Regional Association, 1924-1925 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Southeastern Regional Association, 1932-1939 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Regional Association of General Chairmen - Western (Transportation Communication Union), 1969 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Regional Association of General Chairmen - Western: Newsletter, 1966-1971 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Regional Association of General Chairmen - Western, 1965-1969 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    January 1965-February 1969
  - Western Regional Association of System and/or Terminal Boards of Adjustment, 1933-1938 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Western Regional Association of System and/or Terminal Boards of Adjustment, 1929-1932 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Western Regional Association - Meeting Minutes, 1931 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Western Regional Association - Meeting Minutes, 1931-1932 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Western Regional Association - Meeting Minutes, 1929 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Western Regional Association - Correspondence, 1926-1927 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Rules and Hearings, 1924 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Regional Association of General Chairmen - Express Division, 1963-1974 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - National Association of Express General Chairmen, 1961-1962 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - National Association of Express General Chairmen, 1940-1960 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Association of Railway Express General Chairmen, 1929-1939 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Eastern Regional Association - Meeting Minutes, 1930-1932 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Western Regional Association, 1929 (Box 120, Folder 19)
- 469 2-540-0 (Box 121)
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement - Awards - Section 13 Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    November 1, 1962-January 31, 1963
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement - Awards - Section 13 Committee, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    February-December 1963
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement - Awards - Section 13 Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    January 1, 1964-August 4, 1966
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement - Section 13 Committee - 1964 Meeting and Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    1964-June 4, 1965
  - United States Government - Department of Transportation, 1972-1974 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    1972-October 1974
  - Pensions - Supplemental, 1952-1972 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Political Expenditures - Protests, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    April-December 1974
  - National Transportation Policy, 1963-1972 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    June 1963-December 1972
- 544 - 0-900 (Box 122)
  - Bankrupt Railroads - "Federail" HR 7373, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    January-August 1973
  - Bankrupt Railroads - "Federail" HR 7373, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    September 1, 1973-March 31, 1974
  - Bankruptcy - Railway Express Agency (REA), 1975 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    January-December 8, 1975
  - Bankruptcy - Railway Express Agency (REA), 1975 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    December 8-19, 1975
  - Bankruptcy - Railway Express Agency (REA), 1975-1976 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    December 20, 1975-January 8, 1976
  - Bankruptcy - Railway Express Agency (REA), 1976 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    January 9-18, 1976
- 553 - 4- (Box 123)
  - Mergers - United Transport Service Employees, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO); Minutes of the General Executive Board Meeting, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    September 17, 1972.
  - Mergers - United Transport Service Employees; Minutes of the Eighteenth Biennial Constitutional Convention, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    September 18-19, 1972
  - Merger - United Transport Service Employees, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Agreements Between United Transport Service Employees and Pennsylvania Railroad, 1940-1969 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - United Transport Service Employees Reorganization of Penn Central Railroad, 1971-1972 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Organizational Merger - United Transport Service Employees (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Organizational Merger - United Transport Service Employees and Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks, 1971-1973 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Job Corps National, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Merger - United Transport Service Employees/Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks - Membership Lists by Local, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of General Executive Board Meeting, United Transport Service Employees, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    September 17, 1972
  - Annuities - Disability, 1958-1967 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Annuities - Survivors, 1964-1965 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Child's Annuities, 1964-1966 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Parents' Annuities (Box 123, Folder 14)
    Found Empty February 21, 2015
  - Pensions - Veterans (Military Service Credits, Effect on Annuities), 1958-1960 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Annuities (General), 1965-1967 (Box 123, Folder 16)
- Railroad Retirement (Box 124)
  - Railroad Retirement - General Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Amendments to the Railroad Retirement Act - Eligibility for full annuity after 30 years, 1967-1968 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Retirement Act - Constitutionality, 1934-1958 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Amendments - Railroad Retirement Act, 1963-1970 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Educational Conferences, 1964-1969 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Review, 1968-1969 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Retirement Board Personnel, 1957-1969 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Briefs and Rulings - Electric Lines, Municipal Bridges, Railroad Subsidiaries, 1938-1961 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Railway Express Agency (REA) versus Railroad Retirement Board (RRB) - Application for Retirement and Unemployment Insurance, Acts to Joint Agents and Express Agency (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Actuarial Reports and Data, 1957-1969 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Railroad Retirement Fund Reserve, 1956-1962 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Railroad Retirement - Taxes, 1960-1965 (Box 124, Folder 12)
- Railroad Retirement (Box 125)
  - United States Congress - Civil Rights Act, 1965-1967 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - United States Congress - Age Discrimination in Employment Act, 1967 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Reciprocal Trade Agreements, 1955-1959 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    March 17, 1955-1959
  - Air Mail Pay, 1952 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Millionaires Amendment, 1951-1959 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Mutual Security Act, 1956-1959 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Acts of Congress - Highway Program, 1957-1959 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    July 1957-1959
  - Welfare and Pension Fund Disclosure Legislation, 1958-1963 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    April 13, 1958-1963
  - Transportation Taxes, 1955-1958 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Hells Canyon Dam, 1953-1958 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Legislation Regulating Labor Unions, 1958 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - United States Congress - Civil Rights Act, 1968-1969 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    September 1968-December 1969
  - United States Congress - Civil Rights Act, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    January-August 1968
- Railroad Retirement (Box 126)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - General Correspondence, 1938-1969 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Taxes, 1940-1959 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Personnel, 1939-1940 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Claims, Strike and Instructions, 1949-1967 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Employment, 1957-1961 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Express Commissions, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Amendments, 1957-1962 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Procedures under the Act, 1947-1968 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Acts - Claims (Unemployment), 1961-1969 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Claims (Sickness and Injury), 1958-1967 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act - Claims (Maternity) (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Canadian Unemployment Insurance Act - General Correspondence, 1941-1965 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Canadian Unemployment Insurance Act - Copy, 1940-1963 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Canadian Unemployment Insurance Act - Amendments, 1961-1962 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Canadian Unemployment Insurance Act - Advisory Committee, 1940-1961 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Canadian Unemployment Insurance Act - Application to United States Employees, 1940-1941 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Canadian Unemployment Insurance Act - Questionnaire on Local Lodges and Employees under Railroad Retirement Act, 1939-1940 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Regulation of Labor Unions - Registration of Labor Organizations having members engaged in interstate and foreign commerce, 1948-1959 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    April 1948-1959
  - National Defense, 1950-1959 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    August 1950-1959
  - National Defense - Selective Service Act, 1953-1958 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Transportation Act, 1940-1962 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    November 1940-February 1962
  - Revenue Act, 1953-1962 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    August 1953-July 1962
  - Unemployment Benefits (States), 1961-1963 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - United States Congress - Interstate Commerce Act (Proposed Amendments), 1961-1963 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    May 6, 1961-April 30, 1963
- Railroad Retirement (Box 127)
  - Railroad Retirement - HR 7200, etcetera, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Retirement Commission - Miscellaneous (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - President's Commission on Railroad Retirement (File 1), 1971 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    January-May 1971
  - President's Commission on Railroad Retirement (File 2), 1971 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    May-July 1971
  - President's Commission on Railroad Retirement (File 3), 1971 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    April-October 1971
  - President's Commission on Railroad Retirement (File 3-A), 1971 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    October-December 1971
  - President's Commission on Railroad Retirement (File 4), 1972 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Grievances- Railway Express Agency (REA) - South Atlantic Department Appeal, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Grievances- Railway Express Agency (REA) - South Atlantic Department Appeal, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Grievances- Railway Express Agency (REA) - South Atlantic Department Appeal, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - United States Government Memorandums (Box 127, Folder 9)